Senate fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Senate Committees, 1965 - 1987; F-84-1; 13.72 m of textual records
  - Senate Committee on Graduate Studies (SCGS), 1966 - 1986; F-84-1-9; 4.82 m of textual records
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 1983, F-84-1-9-0-224 (Archival box - standard 84-94)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 1983, F-84-1-9-0-225 (Archival box - standard 84-95)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 1983, F-84-1-9-0-226 (Archival box - standard 84-95)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 1983, F-84-1-9-0-227 (Archival box - standard 84-95)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Jan. 1984, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-228 (Archival box - standard 84-95)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Jan. 1984, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-229 (Archival box - standard 84-95)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. - Mar. 1984, F-84-1-9-0-230 (Archival box - standard 84-95)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 1984, F-84-1-9-0-231 (Archival box - standard 84-95)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 1984, F-84-1-9-0-232 (Archival box - standard 84-96)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. - Aug. 1984, F-84-1-9-0-233 (Archival box - standard 84-96)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 1984, F-84-1-9-0-234 (Archival box - standard 84-96)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 1984, F-84-1-9-0-235 (Archival box - standard 84-96)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. - Dec. 1984, F-84-1-9-0-236 (Archival box - standard 84-96)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Jan. 1985, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-237 (Archival box - standard 84-97)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Jan. 1985, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-238 (Archival box - standard 84-97)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. - Apr. 1985, F-84-1-9-0-239 (Archival box - standard 84-97)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Apr. 1985, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-240 (Archival box - standard 84-97)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Apr. 1985, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-241 (Archival box - standard 84-97)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 1985, F-84-1-9-0-242 (Archival box - standard 84-97)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. July - Aug. 1985, F-84-1-9-0-243 (Archival box - standard 84-97)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Aug. 1985, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-244 (Archival box - standard 84-98)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Aug. 1985, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-245 (Archival box - standard 84-98)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 1985, F-84-1-9-0-246 (Archival box - standard 84-98)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Nov. 1985, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-247 (Archival box - standard 84-98)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Nov. 1985, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-248 (Archival box - standard 84-98)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 1985, F-84-1-9-0-249 (Archival box - standard 84-98)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Jan. 1986, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-250 (Archival box - standard 84-98)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Jan. 1986, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-251 (Archival box - standard 84-98)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Jan. 1986, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-252 (Archival box - small 84-99)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. - Mar. 1986, F-84-1-9-0-253 (Archival box - small 84-99)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. July 1986, F-84-1-9-0-254 (Archival box - small 84-99)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 1986, F-84-1-9-0-255 (Archival box - small 84-99)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 1986, F-84-1-9-0-256 (Archival box - small 84-99)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 1986, F-84-1-9-0-257 (Archival box - small 84-99)
    - Senate Committee on Graduate Studies index, 1966 - 1978; F-84-1-9-0-258 (Archival box - standard 84-109)
    - Senate Committee on Graduate Studies index, 1966 - 1978; F-84-1-9-0-259 (Archival box - standard 84-109)
  - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, 1978 - 1981; F-84-1-10; 38 cm of textual records
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1978 - 1979; F-84-1-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-100)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1978 - 1979; F-84-1-10-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-100)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 3, vol. 3, 1978 - 1979; F-84-1-10-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-100)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1978 - 1980; F-84-1-10-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-100)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1978 - 1980; F-84-1-10-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-100)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 3, vol. 3, 1978 - 1980; F-84-1-10-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-100)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 4, vol. 4, 1978 - 1980; F-84-1-10-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-101)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 1. May - June 1980, vol. 1, F-84-1-10-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-101)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 2. Mar. - April 1980, vol. 2, F-84-1-10-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-101)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 3. Feb. - Mar. 1980, vol. 3, F-84-1-10-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-101)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 4. Jan. - Feb. 1980, vol. 4, F-84-1-10-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-101)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 1. Nov. 1980, vol. 1, F-84-1-10-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-101)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 2. Nov. 1980, vol. 2, F-84-1-10-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-102)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 3. June - Oct. 1980, vol. 3, F-84-1-10-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-102)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 4. June - July 1980, vol. 4, F-84-1-10-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-102)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1980 - 1981; F-84-1-10-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-102)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1980 - 1981; F-84-1-10-0-17 (Archival box - standard 84-102)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 3, vol. 3, 1980 - 1981; F-84-1-10-0-18 (Archival box - standard 84-102)
    - Senate Committee to Consider Student Academic Discipline and Conduct, vol. 4, vol. 4, 1980 - 1981; F-84-1-10-0-19 (Archival box - standard 84-102)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Graduate Program Assessment Committee, 1972 - 1985; F-84-1-11; 38 cm of textual records
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Communications (MA), 1972; F-84-1-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-103)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - French, Teaching of (MA), 1972; F-84-1-11-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-103)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Kinesiology (PhD), 1972; F-84-1-11-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-103)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Pest Management (MPM), 1972 - 1973; F-84-1-11-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-103)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - English (PhD), 1973; F-84-1-11-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-103)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Kinesiology (PhD), 1974; F-84-1-11-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-103)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Political Science, Criminology, BioScience, 1975; F-84-1-11-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-104)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - French, Teaching of / MPM / Communications, 1976; F-84-1-11-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-104)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Psychology (MA and PhD), 1977; F-84-1-11-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-104)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Computing Science, 1978; F-84-1-11-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-104)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Education (MEd)/Computing Sc. (MAandPhD)/English, Teaching of as 2nd Language, 1978; F-84-1-11-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-104)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Resource Management (MRM), 1978; F-84-1-11-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-104)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Business Admin (MBA), 1981; F-84-1-11-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-105)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Communications (PhD), 1981; F-84-1-11-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-105)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Education (PhD), 1981; F-84-1-11-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-105)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Women's Studies, 1982; F-84-1-11-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-105)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Statistics, 1983; F-84-1-11-0-17 (Archival box - standard 84-105)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Criminology (PhD), 1984; F-84-1-11-0-18 (Archival box - standard 84-105)
    - Grad Prog. Assessment Cttee - Engineering (MEng.; MASc.), 1985; F-84-1-11-0-19 (Archival box - standard 84-105)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on Kinesiology, 1967; F-84-1-12; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Ad hoc Committee on Kinesiology - background report. Jan. 1967, F-84-1-12-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Committee on Student Representation and Openess of Senate Meetings, 1967; F-84-1-13; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Cttee on Student Representation and Openness of Senate meetings - report. Jan. 1967, F-84-1-13-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee to Recommend Preocedures for the Election of Student Representatives to Senate, 1967; F-84-1-14; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Ad hoc Cttee to Recommend Preocedures for the Election of Student Representatives to Senate - paper 3A. Feb. 1967, F-84-1-14-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on General Education, 1967; F-84-1-15; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Ad hoc Cttee on General Education. Mar. 1967, F-84-1-15-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Committee on Liberalisation and Education, 1967; F-84-1-16; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Cttee on Liberalisation and Education - report. Apr. 1967, F-84-1-16-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Committee on Senate-Board Working Relations, 1967 - 1968; F-84-1-17; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Cttee on Senate-Board Working Relations - correspondence, 1967 - 1968; F-84-1-17-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee to Investigate Allegations of Non-Professional Conduct, 1968; F-84-1-18; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Ad hoc Cttee to Investigate Allegations of Non-Professional Conduct - report. May 1968, F-84-1-18-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Ciommittee to Study Constitution and Functions of Governing Bodies of the University, 1968; F-84-1-19; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Ad hoc Cttee to Study Constitution and Functions of Governing Bodies of the University - report. May 1968, F-84-1-19-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on Methods of Appointment, Tenure and Function of Deans and Department Heads, 1968; F-84-1-20; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Ad hoc Cttee on Methods of Appointment, Tenure and Function of Deans and Department Heads - report. Sept. 1968, F-84-1-20-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on Faculty Status, 1968 - 1970; F-84-1-21; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Ad hoc Cttee on Faculty Status, 1968 - 1970; F-84-1-21-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on Degree Programs for Part-Time Students, 1970 - 1972; F-84-1-22; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Ad hoc Cttee on Degree Programs for Part-Time Students. Sept. 1970 - Mar. 1972, 1970 - 1972; F-84-1-22-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Ad hoc Cttee to Review Senate Procedures and Establish Codification, 1968 - 1973; F-84-1-23; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Ad hoc Cttee to Review Senate Procedures and Establish Codification, 1968 - 1973; F-84-1-23-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on Alternative Academic Philosophies and Academic Objectives for SFU, 1974 - 1975; F-84-1-24; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Ad hoc Cttee on Alternative Academic Philosophies and Academic Objectives for SFU, 1974 - 1975; F-84-1-24-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Committee on Undergraduate Studies Sub-Committee on Grading, 1972 - 1975; F-84-1-25; 1 cm of textual records
    - SCUS Sub- committee on Grading, 1972 - 1975; F-84-1-25-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-106)
  - Senate Ad Hoc Committee on Rules and Procedures Pertaining to Professional Conduct, 1971; F-84-1-26; 2 cm of textual records
    - Senate Ad hoc Cttee on Rules and Procedures Pertaining to Professional Conduct, 1971; F-84-1-26-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-107)
  - Senate Committee to Consider Faculty Ethics and Responsibilities, 1971 - 1982; F-84-1-27; 2 cm of textual records
    - Senate Cttee to Consider Faculty Ethics and Responsibilities, 1971 - 1982; F-84-1-27-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-107)
  - Senate Committee to Hear Grade Appeals, 1980 - 1984; F-84-1-28; 6 cm of textual records
    - Senate Committee to Hear Grade Appeals, 1980 - 1981; F-84-1-28-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-107)
    - Senate Committee to Hear Grade Appeals, 1981 - 1982; F-84-1-28-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-107)
    - Senate Committee to Hear Grade Appeals, 1981 - 1983; F-84-1-28-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-107)
    - Senate Committee to Hear Grade Appeals, 1981 - 1984; F-84-1-28-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-107)
  - Senate Committee on Committees, 1975; F-84-1-29; 7 cm of textual records
    - Senate Committee on Committees, vol. 1. June 1975, vol. 1, F-84-1-29-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-107)
    - Senate Committee on Committees, vol. 2. June - July 1975, vol. 2, F-84-1-29-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-107)
    - Senate Committee on Committees, vol. 3. July 1975, vol. 3, F-84-1-29-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-108)
    - Senate Committee on Committees, vol. 4. Sept. 1975, vol. 4, F-84-1-29-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-108)
  - Senate Committee on Examination and Grading Practices, 1967 - 1970; F-84-1-30; 4 cm of textual records
    - Senate Committee on Examination and Grading Practices, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1967 - 1970; F-84-1-30-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-108)
    - Senate Committee on Examination and Grading Practices, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1967 - 1970; F-84-1-30-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-108)
  - Senate Agenda Committee, 1969 - 1973; F-84-1-31; 4 cm of textual records
    - Senate Agenda Committee, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1969 - 1973; F-84-1-31-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-108)
    - Senate Agenda Committee, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1969 - 1973; F-84-1-31-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-108)
  - Senate Nominating Committee, 1967 - 1982; F-84-1-32; 8 cm of textual records
    - Senate Agenda Committee, 1967 - 1969; F-84-1-32-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-109)
    - Senate Agenda Committee, 1970; F-84-1-32-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-109)
    - Senate Agenda Committee, 1971; F-84-1-32-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-109)
    - Senate Agenda Committee, 1972 - 1973; F-84-1-32-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-109)
    - Senate Agenda Committee, 1974 - 1975; F-84-1-32-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-109)
    - Senate Agenda Committee, 1982; F-84-1-32-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-109)
  - Senate Committee on Undergraduate Admissions and Standings, 1966 - 1967; F-84-1-33; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Committee on Undergraduate Admissions and Standings, 1966 - 1967; F-84-1-33-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-109)
  - Senate Committee on Graduate Admissions, 1969 - 1970; F-84-1-34; 1 cm of textual records
    - Senate Committee on Graduate Admissions, 1969 - 1970; F-84-1-34-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-109)
  - Senate Committee on Scholarships, Awards and Bursaries, 1971 - 1986; F-84-1-35; 76 cm of textual records
    - SCSAB - members and terms of reference, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1972 - 1984; F-84-1-35-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-118)
    - SCSAB - members, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1972 - 1984; F-84-1-35-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-118)
    - SCSAB - members, vol. 3, vol. 3, 1972 - 1984; F-84-1-35-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-118)
    - SCSAB - annual reports, 1971 - 1972; F-84-1-35-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-118)
    - SCSAB - annual reports, 1973 - 1975; F-84-1-35-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-118)
    - SCSAB - annual reports, 1976 - 1977; F-84-1-35-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-118)
    - SCSAB - annual reports, 1977 - 1981; F-84-1-35-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-118)
    - SCSAB - annual reports, 1982 - 1986; F-84-1-35-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-119)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Mar. 27 - Dec. 20, 1973, vol. 1, F-84-1-35-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-119)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Feb. 9 - Sept. 24, 1973, vol. 2, F-84-1-35-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-119)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Feb. 14 - Dec. 4, 1974, vol. 1, F-84-1-35-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-119)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Jan. 30 - Sept. 27, 1974, vol. 2, F-84-1-35-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-119)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Aug. - Dec. 12, 1975, vol. 1, F-84-1-35-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-119)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Mar. 18 - Sept. 30, 1975, vol. 2, F-84-1-35-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-119)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Jan. 29 - Dec. 17, 1975, vol. 3, F-84-1-35-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-119)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 4. Jan. 28 - Dec. 18, 1975, vol. 4, F-84-1-35-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-120)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. June 1 - Dec. 14, 1976, vol. 1, F-84-1-35-0-17 (Archival box - standard 84-120)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Jan. 28 - Dec. 15, 1976, vol. 2, F-84-1-35-0-18 (Archival box - standard 84-120)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Jan. 28 - Nov. 15, 1976, vol. 3, F-84-1-35-0-19 (Archival box - standard 84-120)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Feb. 10 - Dec. 14, 1977, vol. 1, F-84-1-35-0-20 (Archival box - standard 84-120)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Jan. 19 - Sept. 29, 1977, vol. 2, F-84-1-35-0-21 (Archival box - standard 84-120)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Mar. 20 - Dec. 10, 1980, vol. 1, F-84-1-35-0-22 (Archival box - standard 84-120)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Feb. 6 - Nov. 19, 1980, vol. 2, F-84-1-35-0-23 (Archival box - standard 84-121)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Jan. 22 - Dec 8, 1981, vol. 1, F-84-1-35-0-24 (Archival box - standard 84-121)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Feb. 4 - Nov. 13, 1981, vol. 2, F-84-1-35-0-25 (Archival box - standard 84-121)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Sept. 27 - Dec. 9, 1982, vol. 1, F-84-1-35-0-26 (Archival box - standard 84-121)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Feb. 16 - Sept. 10, 1982, vol. 2, F-84-1-35-0-27 (Archival box - standard 84-121)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Feb. 3 - June 29, 1982, vol. 3, F-84-1-35-0-28 (Archival box - standard 84-121)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. June 7 - Nov. 3, 1983, vol. 1, F-84-1-35-0-29 (Archival box - standard 84-122)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Feb. 1 - May 17, 1983, vol. 2, F-84-1-35-0-30 (Archival box - standard 84-122)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Oct. 4 - Dec. 11, 1984, vol. 1, F-84-1-35-0-31 (Archival box - standard 84-122)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. May 9 - Sept. 4, 1984, vol. 2, F-84-1-35-0-32 (Archival box - standard 84-122)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Jan. 4 - Apr. 16, 1984, vol. 3, F-84-1-35-0-33 (Archival box - standard 84-122)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Oct. 3 - Dec. 6, 1985, vol. 1, F-84-1-35-0-34 (Archival box - small 84-123)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Apr. 24 - July 25, 1985, vol. 2, F-84-1-35-0-35 (Archival box - small 84-123)
    - SCSAB - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Jan. 24 - Mar 19, 1985, vol. 3, F-84-1-35-0-36 (Archival box - small 84-123)
- Senate - Registrar's correspondence, 1967 - 1973; F-84-2; 12 cm of textual records
  This series consists of records relating to the general conduct of Senate business by the Registrar as Secretary of Senate.
  Activities, events and topics documented include setting agendas and meeting times, changes to minutes, preparation of supporting papers, transmittal of reports and other information to members of the University community, Senate elections, and Senate procedures.
  Records include correspondence, draft minutes with some detailed accounts of discussion, notes, reports, Senate supporting papers, lists of committee members, and committee terms of reference. Two files contain correspondence regarding the replacement of Senate committee members who were unable to complete their terms.
  The files were arranged by the archivist.
  - Registrar's correspondence - general. June 1967, F-84-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-110)
  - Registrar's correspondence - general. July 1967, F-84-2-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-110)
  - Registrar's correspondence - general. Aug. 1967, F-84-2-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-110)
  - Registrar's correspondence - general. Sept. 1967, F-84-2-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-110)
  - Registrar's correspondence - general. Oct. 1967, F-84-2-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-110)
  - Registrar's correspondence - general. Nov. 1967, F-84-2-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-110)
  - Registrar's correspondence - general. Dec. 1967, F-84-2-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-110)
  - Registrar's correspondence - general. Jan. 1968, F-84-2-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-110)
  - Registrar's correspondence - general. Feb. 1968, F-84-2-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-110)
  - Corresponence regarding committee replacements, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1971 - 1973; F-84-2-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-110)
  - Corresponence regarding committee replacements, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1971 - 1973; F-84-2-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-110)
- Senate subject files, 1968 - 1984; F-84-3; 38 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to various issues considered by Senate.
  Activities, events and topics documented include the Admissions Crisis of 1968, which resulted in a student sit-in to protest the lack of transfer credit standards. The Ellis Report, described in another file in this series, was the University's response to that crisis. Examples of other topics include the appointment of a Dean of Graduate Studies and the development of a Co-op Studies Program.
  Records include correspondence, Senate papers and minutes, reports, proposals, notes, and other documents.
  - Admissions crisis, 1968; F-84-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-111)
  - Ellis report, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1969; F-84-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-111)
  - Ellis report, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1969; F-84-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-111)
  - Ellis report, vol. 3, vol. 3, 1969; F-84-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-111)